Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Loretta Simon, 1979-1997; 4; 13.27 cubic ft.
  - Projects, 1979-1997; 4.3; 11.0 cubic ft.
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1995 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1995 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1996 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1996 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1997 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Reports, Undated (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Reports, Undated (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Reports, Undated (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Roundtable Responses, 1995 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Saratoga, Truck By-pass, 1995-1997 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Scenic Byways, 1966 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Scherman Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Seven Point Plan, 1992-1994 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Surface Transit Policy Project (STPP), 1993 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Syracuse Metropolitan Transportation Council, Memorandums and Agendas, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Testimony, 1992; 1994 (Box 9 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Thruway Authority, Niagara, 1994 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Transit, General, 1996 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Transit, Pre-1992, 1981-1983 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Transit, Pre-1992, 1984-1988 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Transportation Alternative, 1991-1993 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, "Transportation Spending in New York: The Path Not Taken", Loretta Simon, Undated (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Ad Campaign, 1995 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Committee, 1995 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Defense Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Defense Fund, 1995 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Defense Fund, Undated (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Funding, 1995 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1980; 1991-1993 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, June 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1993 September (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1993 November (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1994 February (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1994 March (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1994 May (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1995 February (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, April 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, May 1995, 1991 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1995 Summer (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1995 November (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1995 December (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1996 January (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, General, 1996 February (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Meetings, 1996 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 10 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 29)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Mobilizing the Region, 1996 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Retreat, 1994 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Retreat, 1995 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Retreat, Notebook, 1995 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Tri-State Transportation Campaign, Work Plans, 1995 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 11 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
- General Correspondence, 1984-1989; 5; 1.0 cubic ft.
  The General Correspondence series contains original and typescript drafts of incoming and outgoing correspondence.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - General Correspondence, 1984 January 01-1984 May 29 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 June 06-1984 September 26 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 October 01-1984 December 31 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1985 January 30-1985 April 30 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1985 May 02-1985 September 24 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1985 October 03-1985 December 30 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 January 02-1986 February 28 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 March 03-1986 May 30 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 June 01-1986 August 25 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 September 02-1986 December 29 (Box 1 (5-General Correspondence), Folder 10)
- Publications, 1972-2006; 6; 3.0 cubic ft.
  The Publications series contains material published by the Environmental Advocates as well as material published by others, but collected by the Environmental Advocates. The series is divided into two subseries: Environmental Advocates Publications and Publications of Others. The series occupies 3.0 cubic feet; the inclusive dates are 1972-2000, with bulk dates of 1986-1992.
  - Environmental Advocates Publications, 1972-2004; 6.1; 1.0 cubic ft.
    Environmental Advocates' publications are arranged alphabetically by publication title. Titles of interest include the Albany Report -- the bimonthly newsletter of what is happening in New York regarding environmental issues, The Green Sheet - EA's monthly bulletin of statewide environmental activism, and the Voter's Guide. The inclusive dates are 1972-2000 with bulk dates of 1990-1998.
    - Albany Report, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Albany Report, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Albany Report, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Albany Report, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Albany Report, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Albany Report, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Albany Report, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Albany Report, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Albany Report, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Albany Report, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Albany Report, 1999-2004 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Chlorine, Human Health, and the Environment: The Breast Cancer Report, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Environmental Advocates, Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Environmental Planning Lobby, Agenda, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Environmental Planning Lobby, Member Application, Undated (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Garbage In/Garbage Out: A Hard Look at Mixed Municipal Solid Waste Composting, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Garbage In/Garbage Out: A Hard Look at Mixed Municipal Solid Waste Composting, Draft, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Green Sheet, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Green Sheet, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Green Sheet, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Green Sheet, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Green Sheet, 2000-2004 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Green Sheets: A Survey of the Status and Needs of Street Trees in New York's Cities, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 23)
    - In Praise of E.P.L.: Celebrating the Environment 1969-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Public Transportation for a Livable New York, Brochure, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Shortchanged: New York State and the Land and Water Conservation Fund, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Shortchanged: New York State and the Land and Water Conservation Fund, Drafts, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Shortchanged: New York State and the Land and Water Conservation Fund, Drafts, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Shortchanged: New York State and the Land and Water Conservation Fund, Photographs, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Shortchanged: New York State and the Land and Water Conservation Fund, Printers Reference Copy, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Speaking Out for the Environment, Donation Solicitation, Undated (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Tools for Action: A Citizen's Handbook on New York State's Superfund Program, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Transportation Spending in New York: The Path Not Taken, Drafts, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Transportation Spending in New York: The Path Not Taken, Drafts, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Name Change, Mailing Advertisement, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Environmental Protection and Economic Growth...New York Can Have Both, Mailing, Undated (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Your Right to Know: To Protect You and Your Family's Health, Undated (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Voters' Guide, 1972-1979 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Voters' Guide, 1980-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Voters' Guide, 1990-2004; 2006 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Issues in Focus, Undated (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 41)
  - Publications of Others, 1975-2002; 6.2; 2.0 cubic ft.
    The Publications of Others subseries is arranged alphabetically by publication title. Titles of interest include, Adirondack, AGENDA, Catskill Center News, Hudson Valley Green Times, New York Environmental News, Scenic Hudson News, and Upstate Environment (formerly Link). The inclusive dates are 1975-1994 with bulk dates of 1986-1993.
    - Acid Precipitation Digest, 1983; 1986; 1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Action/Action Bulletin, 1982-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Adirondack, 1982; 1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Adirondack Advocate, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Adirondack Council, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Adirondack Council, Special Report, 1982-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Adirondack Update, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Agenda: New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPRIG), 1982-1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Association News, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Audubon Wildlife Bulletin, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Bronx River Restoration, Update, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
    - The Butterfly Effect (formerly Pandora's Box), 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Capital Eyes, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Catskill Center News, 1982-1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Catskill Center Newslette, 1989-1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Center for Environmental Information (CEI) Sphere, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Center for Environmental Information (CEI), Annual Report, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Central New York Environment, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 18)
    - City Limits, 1983; 1985; 1986 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Clearwater Navigator, 1984; 1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Concerned Citizens of Essex County, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Cycle: The Membership Newsletter of the Environmental Coalition, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Don't Waste New York, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 23)
    - The Egg: A Journal of Eco-Justice, 1986-1990 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady, 1984-1986; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Environmental Policy Institute: Perspectives, 1984 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Environment Reporter, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Fertility on the Brink, The Legacy of the Chemical Age, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 28)
    - From the Ground Up: Environmental Law and Practice for the Hudson Valley, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Gaining Altitude, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Garbage Guide (Environmental Action Foundation), 1975; 1977; 1979 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Hazardous Waste Information Focus on New York State, 1986 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 32)
    - The Hudson Valley Green Times, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 33)
    - The Hudson Valley Green Times, 1985-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 34)
    - The Hudson Valley Green Times, 1990; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Inform Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Lake George Association News, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Lake Champlain Committee Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Land Use Law Reporter, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Listings Catalog: A Nonprofit Information Clearinghouse for Waste and Reuse Value, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Long Island Groundwater Management Program, Draft, Department of Environmental Conservation, 1983 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 43)
    - LighTrail Newsletter, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 44)
    - The Green Drummer, Undated (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Environmental Update, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 46)
    - The Examiner, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Alabama Environmental Council State News, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Empire State Report, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Environmental Law in New York, 1991-1996 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Fifty Simple Things You can do to Save the Earth, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Adirondack Voices, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Adirondack Park Agency Newsline, 1985 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Environmental Law in New York, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) Newsline, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
    - New England Environmental Network News, 1984-1987 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
    - New Jersey Environmental Lobby News, 1981-1986 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
    - New York Can: Can News, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
    - New York Environmental News (NYEN), 1983-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
    - New York Waste Reporter, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
    - New York State Energy Office, 1983-1987 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
    - New York State Environment, 1982 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
    - New York State Environmental Facilities Corporation, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
    - New York State Environmental Congress Directory, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
    - New York State Environmental Congress Directory, Draft, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
    - The News Bulletin of the National Coalition Against the Misuse of Pesticides (NCAMP), Technical Report, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Northwest Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides, Annual Report, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Nonpoint Assessment Report, Draft, Department of Environmental Conservation, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Northeastern Farmland Update, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Oceanwatch, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 16)
    - The Outdoor Path, 1982 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 17)
    - People for Animal Rights (PARS), 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Pesticides and You, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 19)
    - The Pinelander, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 20)
    - The Powerline, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Preservation League of New York State, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Public Citizen, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Rain, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Resources: Environmental Task Force, 1981-1986 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Ripples, 1984-1986 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Scenic America Publications, 1990-1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1982-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Sierra Club, Various, 1980-1989 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Solutions, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Toxics in Your Community, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Tug Hill Commission Newsletter, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Up River/Down River, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Upper Hudson Environmental Action Committee, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Upstate Environment (formerly Link), 1982-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Waste Not, 1988-1995 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Where We Stand, Informational Brochure, Association for the Protection of the Adirondacks, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Who Pays... and Why, Undated (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Women and the Environment, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Your Office Paper Recycling Guide, Undated (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Wetlands News, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 41)
    - New York State Lamplight, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Peer Review, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Rachel's Hazardous Waste News, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 44)
    - River Watch, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Waste and Toxics Progress Report, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Trail Walker, 1982-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 47)
    - The Proposed Saint Lawrence Cement Plant in Greenport and Hudson, 2002 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 48)
- Audio Visuals, 1989-1995; 7; 1.4 cubic ft.
  - Audio, 1989-1992; 7.1; 9 audiotapes
    The Audio subseries contains nine audiotapes. There are two tapes from the 20th Anniversary Dinner in 1989. Dick Cavett served as the master of ceremonies at the dinner and speakers included Lee Wasserman, David Sive, Gov. Mario Cuomo, Tom Chapin, Robert Abrams, Sigourney Weaver, and Warren Liebold. Other audiotapes in the series include radio advertisements targeting state legislators and promoting events.
    - Radio Advertisement, Senator Hugh T. Farley and Drinking Water, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 1)
    - Radio Advertisement, Senators Ralph J. Marino and Dean G. Skelos and Water Protection, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 2)
    - 20th Anniversary, Dick Cavett, Lee Wasserman, David Sive, Gov. Mario Cuomo (New York), Tom Chapin, Attorney General Robert Abrams, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 3)
    - 20th Anniversary, Dick Cavett, Sigourney Weaver, Warren Liebold, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 4)
    - Radio Advertisement, Senator Nicholas A. Spano and Drinking Water, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 5)
    - Lee Wasserman discussing the Bonnie Raitt Concert for Women's Health, WNEW-FM, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 6)
    - Clean Air Promo, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 7)
    - Ask the Governor, WCBS, 1992 June 18 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Cassette 8)
  - Moving Images, 1989-1995; 7.2; 9 videotapes
    The Moving Images subseries primarily contains VHS tapes, along with one Sony Video 8 tape. The subject matter of the tapes include issues related to pesticides, energy (James Bay in Quebec), hazardous waste (low-level radioactive waste), lead, funding (Environmental Bond Act), and solid waste management (recycling).
    - Employees To IBM-Kingston, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 1)
    - Environment '90 Animal Rights, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 2)
    - Environment '90 Beyond Earth Day Keynote Speech by Bill McKibben, Author of The End of Nature, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 3)
    - Environment '90 Beyond Earth Day Perspectives on the Adirondack Commission Report for the Next Legislative Session, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 4)
    - Environment '90 Beyond Earth Day Pesticide Residues on Food, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 5)
    - Environment '90 Beyond Earth Day Plenary Session: The 21st Century Environmental Bond Act, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 6)
    - Environment '90 Beyond Earth Day Speech by Department of Environmental Conservation Commissioner Thomas C. Jorling, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 7)
    - Environment '90 BRC Low Level Radioactive Waste, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 8)
    - Environmental Enforcement Act Video, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 9)
    - Environmental Enforcement Act Video, Glatz, 309 Madison St., Westbury, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 10)
    - Environmental Enforcement Act, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 11)
    - Environmental Enforcement Act Video, Undated (Box 1 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 12)
    - External Affairs Canada "Acid Rain: A North American Challenge", Undated (Box 2 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 1)
    - Inside Albany, 1995 (Box 2 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 2)
    - Lead Contamination, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Audio Visuals), Folder 3)